Guide to the Barney Rosset papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series V: Samuel Beckett Material, 1935-2007
  - Subseries V.1: Correspondence, 1953-2005
    - “Beckett-Rosset Correspondence”
      - Gontarski
        - “1960-1989” (Box 47, Folder 10)
        - “1964-1989--Without Notes”, (2 folders) (Box 47, Folder 11-12)
        - “Beckett-Rosset Letters, 1953-1959, (2 folders) (Box 47, Folder 13-14)
        - “Correspondence, Intros, Articles,” 1979 1986-1993 (Box 47, Folder 15)
        - "Edited, 1953-1959" 2006-2008, (2 folders) (Box 47, Folder 16-17)
        - “Sam & Barney Letters & Related Corresp,” 1994-2005 (Box 47, Folder 18)
    - "Beckett-C. Prentice, 1930-1936 1994 (Box 47, Folder 19)
    - "Beckett-Schmidt," 1957-1958 (Box 47, Folder 20)
    - "Beckett-Suhrkamp," 1954-1974 (Box 47, Folder 21)
    - “French, 1950-1959” (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - "Henry Wenning-Samuel Beckett," 1960-1971 1985 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - “Judith Schmidt, Dick Seaver and Others”
      - 1962-1963 (Box 48, Folder 3)
      - 1962-1967 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - "Misc Correspondence," 1982-2000, (2 folders) (Box 48, Folder 5-6)
    - "Production Requests," 1973-1977 1994 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - “Rosset-Beckett-Grove, 1961” (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - "Samuel Beckett Original Letters," 1966-1994 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - “Schmidt / Rosset / Beckett & Others, 1960-1982” (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - "A. Schneider, J. Schneider, Fehsenfeld, Rosset," 1977-1994 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - "Special Letters, 1948-1991 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Sub-subseries V.1.1: Beckett Correspondence Project, 1935-2003
      Contains materials related to a project regarding the publication of Samuel Beckett's correspondence. This sub-sub-series does not include the copies of Beckett's correspondence or teh manuscript of colelction, but it does includes the National Endowment for the Humanities (NEH) application files, correspondence related to the project and other related records.
      - General
        - "Originals 1," 1994-1995, (2 folders) (Box 48, Folder 13-14)
        - “Originals 2,” 1991-1995 (Box 48, Folder 15)
        - "Scans," 1976-2003, (2 folders) (Box 48, Folder 16-17)
        - “Scans & Copies of Originals,” 1976-2003, (2 folders) (Box 48, Folder 18-19)
        - "Timeline Synopsis," 1985-2003 (Box 48, Folder 20)
      - "Agreements & Correspondence," 1976-1991, (2 folders) (Box 48, Folder 21-22)
      - "FOIA-1993 NEH App & Docs," 1993-1998 (Box 49, Folder 1)
      - "Lindon Censorship Beckett Letters," 1935-1982 (Box 49, Folder 2)
      - National Endowment for the Humanities
        - "NEH Application 1989" 1989-1990 (Box 49, Folder 3)
        - "NEH Application 1991" 1989-1991 (Box 49, Folder 4)
        - "NEH Application 1992" 1989-1992 (Box 49, Folder 5)
        - "NEH Application 1993" 1989-1993 (Box 49, Folder 6)
        - "NEH Application 1995" 1995 (Box 49, Folder 7)
        - "NEH Application Excerpts US Code," 1990-1995 (Box 49, Folder 8)
        - "NEH FOIA ONE," 1989-2003 (Box 49, Folder 9)
      - ‘Prospectus, Syracuse Library, U Texas-Austin Library, Contracts, Foreign Rights, Expenses, Permissions, U of FLA Press, B.R. Letters w/Annotation queries,” 1985-1994, (3 folders) (Box 49, Folder 10-12)
  - Subseries V.2: Related Projects, Works, and Affairs, 1949-2007
    Consists of print matter related to Beckett projects, writings and staged plays, correspondence, photographs, and some audio-visual materials in various formats. Information on Beckett play productions (including Eleutheria), the public television Beckett Project, Beckett's Film, revivals, and other projects can be found here.
    - "Beckett Centenary Articles & Interviews with Barney," 2005-2006, (2 folders) (Box 49, Folder 13-14)
    - "The Beckett Circle Article," 1995-2003 (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - "The Beckett Circle Newsletter," 1996-2006 (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - "Beckett-Misc," 1985-2000 (Box 49, Folder 17)
    - "Beckett Prison Project," 1983-1993 (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - "The Beckett Project"
      - "Correspondences and Expenses," 1986-1995 (Box 50, Folder 2)
      - "Global Village Description and PBS Description," 1987-1988, (2 folders) (Box 50, Folder 3-4)
      - "Press Release, Grant App's…Transcripts…" 1970-1992, (3 folders) (Box 50, Folder 5-7)
      - "Reilly," 1987 (Box 50, Folder 8)
      - "Waiting for Beckett Scripts," 1988, (2 folders) (Box 50, Folder 9-10)
    - "Beckett Reviews--Godot and S.Still," 1988-1989 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - "Beckett Studies," 1949-2001 (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - "Boston College," 1995 2005 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - "Card Sharps," 1947-1948 (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - "Cronin Excerpts Last Modernist," Undated (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - Edward Beckett
      - "Edward Beckett," 1986-2007 (Box 50, Folder 16)
      - "Rosset-Ed. Beckett Corres," 1990-1996 (Box 50, Folder 17)
      - "Rosset-Ed. Beckett Correspondence," 1990-1996, (2 folders) (Box 50, Folder 18-19)
    - Eleutheria
      - General, 1985-1995 (1 of 2 folders) (Box 50, Folder 20)
      - General, 1985-1995 (1 of 2 folders) (Box 51, Folder 1)
      - Albert Bermel Translation, 1995 (Box 51, Folder 2)
      - "Beckett in Thailand," 1997-2003 (Box 51, Folder 3)
      - "Contract," 1995-2001 (Box 51, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence, 1979-1995, (2 folders) (Box 51, Folder 5-6)
      - "Correspondence--Grove, Blue Moon," 1979-2003 (Box 51, Folder 7)
      - "Correspondences Lindon-E Beckett-Rosset," 1988-1993 (Box 51, Folder 8)
      - "French Text," Undated (Box 51, Folder 9)
      - "Martin Garbus," 1994-1995 (Box 51, Folder 10)
      - "News Stories and Reviews," 1994-1996 (Box 51, Folder 11)
      - Official Documents, 1994-1995 (Box 51, Folder 12)
      - Readings, Requests, Letters," 1961-1995 (Box 51, Folder 13)
      - "Research," 1995-2004 (Box 51, Folder 14)
      - "Selected Letters," 1993-1995 (Box 51, Folder 15)
      - "Stan Gontarski," 1986-1996 (Box 51, Folder 16)
      - "Thailand," 2000-2003 (Box 51, Folder 17)
      - "Transcript of Panel Discussion," 1995 (Box 51, Folder 18)
      - "Translation by Stan Gontarski," Undated, (2 folders) (Box 51, Folder 19-20)
      - "Working chapter Materials," 1994 (Box 51, Folder 21)
    - "ESQUIRE--Beckett's Last Act," 1990 (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - FILM
      - "Beckett Film," 1969-2004 (Box 52, Folder 2)
      - "Beckett's Film," 1969-2005 (Box 52, Folder 3)
      - "Beckett in Berlin," 2000 (Box 52, Folder 4)
      - Berlin, Tin House, History, Research, 1964-2000 (Box 52, Folder 5)
      - "Copy of Book, Proposal, Script, Publicity," 1969-2000 (Box 52, Folder 6)
      - "Film Requests," 1986-1992, (2 folders) (Box 52, Folder 7-8)
      - "Project I: Three Original Motion Picture Scripts," Undated (Box 52, Folder 9)
      - "Requests to show Film," 1993-2000, (2 folders) (Box 52, Folder 10-11)
      - "Requests to show Film or for Remakes,"1976-2000 (Box 52, Folder 12)
      - "Research on Film," 2005 (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - "Harvard Endgame Press," 1984-2006, (2 folders) (Box 52, Folder 14-15)
    - "Misc Rights Requests," 1955-1997, (2 folders) (Box 52, Folder 16-17)
    - "Newsletter of the Samuel Beckett Society," 2003 (Box 52, Folder 18)
    - "On-Line Resources," 2006 (Box 52, Folder 19)
    - "PEN Beckett Tribute," 2002-2003 (Box 52, Folder 20)
    - "Rosset on Beckett for Beckett Project," 1992 2006 (Box 52, Folder 21)
    - "Samuel French--Dram, Play Serv.," 1974-1994 (Box 52, Folder 22)
    - Stirrings Still
      - General, 1988-2003, (2 folders) (Box 52, Folder 23-24)
      - "Contract Production," 1988 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      - Sales, Solicitations, Buyers, 1988-1990, (2 folders) (Box 53, Folder 2-3)
      - "Text, Galleys, Correspondence," 1986-1988 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - "Susan Sontag," 1969-2009 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - "Talmer Resource," 2001 Undated (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - "Theatrical and Film Contracts--Samuel French, Channel 13, Jack Gardfein, Drama Play Service," 1961-1994, (2 folders) (Box 53, Folder 7-8)
    - "Three Original Motion Picture Scripts by Samuel Beckett, Eugene Ionesco, Harold Pinter," 1963 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - "Translations of Negro 1-12, Intro., Inc.," 1998-1999 Undated (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - "Translations of Negro (Nancy Cunard)," 2000 Undated, (2 folders) (Box 53, Folder 11-12)
    - "University of Reading Beckett Collection," 1990 (Box 53, Folder 13)
    - "Waiting for Godot Video Contracts," 1970-1993 (Box 53, Folder 14)
- Series VI: Audio Visual Materials, 1938-2008
  Largely organized by media format, this series consists mostly VHS tapes, but also contains DVDs, CDs, Beta tapes, 7 inch-Magnetic Audio Reels, along with a few 5 inch reels. 2 Inch Tape, reels, DV Cam, MiniDV, Floppy Disks. There seems to have been an effort by the creator to transfer older formats into digital media, as the titles some of the items are duplicated through being digitally transferred. The reels and other magnetic formats have been put in cold storage.
  - VHS (Box 54)
    - "Beckett/Berg--Happy Days, Bettina Jonic" (Box 54)
    - "Hollywood TV Theatre--Beginning to End" (Box 54)
    - "Five Plays for Television, Dir. By Sidney Homan" (Box 54)
    - "Peephole Art: Beckett for Television" (Box 54)
    - "Silence to Silence" (Box 54)
    - "South of Silence" (Box 54)
    - "PBS Broadcast of 7 Beckett Plays" (Box 54)
    - "BBC TV Omnibus Samuel Beckett--As the Story was Told" (Box 54)
    - "Beckett's Letters" (Box 54)
    - "Waiting for Beckett" (Box 54)
    - "Silence to Silence" (Box 54)
    - "Stirrings Still" (Box 54)
    - "Beckett/Reilly/Rosset--Stirrings Still" (Box 54)
    - "Godot in San Quentin" (Box 54)
    - "Samuel Beckett is Coming Soon" (Box 54)
    - "Waiting for Godot" (Box 54)
    - "Waiting for Godot--Lincoln Center" (Box 54)
    - "Film" (Box 54)
    - "Film--Outtakes" (Box 54)
    - "Film" (Box 54)
    - "Krapp's Last Tape" (Box 54)
    - "Beckett Live Action" (Box 54)
    - "Beckett--Astrid Myers" (Box 54)
    - "Channel 31 Beckett Show with Barney Rosset" (Box 54)
    - "Remember Beckett #101" (Box 54)
    - "As the Story Was Told" (Box 54)
    - "Excerpts from Global Village Production of Stirrings Still" (Box 54)
    - "Waiting for Godot--WNET (1961)" (Box 54)
    - "Rough for Theatre" (Box 54)
    - "Barney Rosset/Steven Watson" (Box 54)
    - "Barney Rosset/Fred Jordan" (Box 54)
    - "Barney Rosset/Fred Jordan" (Box 54)
    - "Steve Martin Interview" (Box 54)
    - "Barney Rosset for the Beckett Project--Global Village" (Box 54)
    - "The Eleventh Hour--TV Panle on Pantheon/Random House" (Box 54)
    - "Barney Rosset Interview for CUNY TV" (Box 54)
    - "Barney Rosset Interview for CUNY TV" (Box 54)
    - "Strange Victory--Master from TV Dubbing" (Box 54)
    - "Rosset Interview with Mark Wexler" (Box 54)
    - "Strange Victory--Not a Good Copy" (Box 54)
    - "Strange Victory" (Box 54)
    - "Strange Victory" (Box 54)
    - "But the Clouds" (Box 54)
    - "Tim Lee" (Box 54)
    - Sex in the 20th Century (Box 55)
      - "Hour 1-The Century Turns On" (Box 55)
      - "Hour 2-Passion's Coming of Age" (Box 55)
      - "Hour 4-The Politics of Pleasure" (Box 55)
    - "Barney Rosset Lecture--Checker Board Sandy Meeham" (Box 55)
    - "Barney Rosset Interview for CUNY TV" (Box 55)
    - "NBCC Award Steve Wasserman/Barney Rosset" (Box 55)
    - "NBCC Award March12, 2001" (Box 55)
    - "Barney Rosset at National Arts Club: WS Burroughs" (Box 55)
    - "Early Works--The Joke" (Box 55)
    - "The Joke" (Box 55)
    - "Grove Press--Int. Film Festival" (Box 55)
    - "Grove Press--Man Alive, I Call It Murder" (Box 55)
    - "Dziga and his Brothers by E. Tsymbal" (Box 55)
    - "Grove Press--Int'L Film Fest. Trailer" (Box 55)
    - "Rockaby" (Box 55)
    - "William Burroughs" (Box 55)
    - "Thanus an Despina" (Box 55)
    - "Rosset Family Movies" (Box 55)
    - "Interview with Barney Rosset on Robert Frank" (Box 55)
    - "Asi Se Vive El Libre Comercio" (Box 55)
    - "Thomas and Despina--Part 1" (Box 55)
    - "Thomas and Despina--Part 2" (Box 55)
    - "Mr. Freedom--Part 2" (Box 55)
    - "Rosy, Rosy" (Box 55)
    - "Sunday Noon Program, CBS" (Box 55)
    - "Writer of O, a Film by Pola Rapaport" (Box 55)
    - "Daughters of the Troubles: Belfast Stories" (Box 55)
    - "The Irish in America" (Box 55)
    - "Meet Marlon Brando" (Box 55)
    - "Five Days in March--Haskell Wexler" (2 copies) (Box 55)
    - "Clint Eastwood--Biography on A& E" (Box 55)
    - "I am Curious Yellow" (Box 55)
    - "Pull My Daisy--Taped from Channel 13" (Box 55)
    - "Weeds--Haskell" (Box 55)
    - "Waiting for the Invasion--Peter Rosset" (Box 55)
    - "Phoebe Legere" (Box 55)
    - "QUEEN" (Box 55)
    - "Quiet Days in Clichy" (Box 55)
    - "Jupiter's Wife" (Box 55)
    - "Haiti Reborn" (Box 55)
    - "Free Zone 2000" (Box 55)
    - "East Hampton Thanksgiving--Surroundings of House" (Box 55)
    - "The Wonderful Horrible Life of Leni Riefenstahl--Part I" (Box 56)
    - "The Wonderful Horrible Life of Leni Riefenstahl--Part II" (Box 56)
    - "Barney Rosset Interview with Al Goldstein" (Box 56)
    - "Pen Award-Rosset" (Box 56)
    - "Barney Rosset--Meeting with Publishers" (Box 56)
    - "ABC News--Interview Barney" (Box 56)
    - "Barney Rosset/Carolyn Somers Meeting--Joan Mitchell Letters" (Box 56)
    - "Barney Rosset Rough Cut" (Box 56)
    - "Barney Rosset and South African Meeting--Two Dogs and Freedom" (Box 56)
    - "Barney Rosset--Football and Venice Footage" (Box 56)
    - "Roussillon/Resistance Section" (Box 56)
    - "Barney Rosset Book for Poor Richard Program" (Box 56)
    - "Sag Harbor Panel on Censorship/Rosset" (Box 56)
    - "Karl Grossman Reports: with Barney Rosset LTV" (Box 56)
    - "Three Magic Theatre Plays" (Box 56)
    - "The Erotic Women of Thailand" (Box 56)
    - "The Good Woman of Bangkok" (Box 56)
    - "Contemporary Haitian Politics" (Box 56)
    - "China 1945--Victory Parade Luichow / Coney Island 1944 Parachute Jump, Roller Coaster (Cyclone)" (Box 56)
    - "Night at the Opera and Other Shorts--Marx Brothers" (Box 56)
    - "Ethnic Cleansing" (Box 56)
    - "Peter Interviewed in NicaraguaÀ" (Box 56)
    - "Pinter People" (Box 56)
    - "Medium Cool" (Box 56)
    - "Tokyo Decadence" (Box 56)
    - "The Battleship Potemkin" (Box 56)
    - "Uprising of '34--Honea Path Remembers After 61 Years" (Box 56)
    - "OE, NBC Nightline" (Box 56)
    - "Naked Lunch" (Box 56)
    - "Interview with Kenzaburo Oe at Barney Rosset's Residence" (Box 56)
    - "Maidstone--Pennebaker Hegedus Films" (Box 56)
    - "Maquila: A tale of two Mexicos" (Box 56)
    - "Office Coy, Sounthern Povety Law Center" (Box 56)
    - "Waldo Salt: A Screenwriter's Journey" (Box 56)
    - "The Road to the Coast" (Box 56)
    - "The Farm by Mac Premo" (Box 56)
  - Samuel Beckett (Box 57)
    - UCLA Film and Television Archive
      - Waiting for Godot
        - Edited Master (Box 57)
        - DVD (Box 57)
        - DVCam (Box 57)
        - DVD (Access Copy) (Box 57)
  - Beta Tape
    - "Rockaby-Barney Rosset Grove Press" (Box 57)
    - "Thanos and Despina--Part 1" (Box 57)
    - "Thanos and Despina, Chant D'Amour--Part 2" (Box 57)
  - Magnetic Recording Tapes
    - "Barney Rosset discussing Grove Press Financial Plan," 1970-1971 À (Box 57)
    - "Barney Rosset Speaking about Censorship" (Box 57)
    - "Grove Recap," 1960 (Box 57)
    - "Use as last rollÀ" (Box 57)
    - "Evergreen Review Presents: Poems to Music and Laughter," 1959 (Box 57)
    - "The Barry Farber Show," 1970 (Box 57)
    - "Feltrinelli on Pasternak" (Box 57)
    - "Evergreen 7 ½ copy of Equalized Tape, Side One" (Box 57)
    - "Judith Crist," 1969 (5 inch tape) (Box 57)
    - Unidentified (5 inch tape) (Box 57)
    - "Ed Rodman," 1960 (Box 57)
    - "Readings from Evergreen Review," ca 1957 (Box 57)
    - "B Grey Dub of April 29, 1969" (Box 57)
    - "Evergreen Review Presents; Feltrinelli and Dr. Zhivago" (Box 57)
    - Blank (Box 57)
    - Blank (Box 57)
    - "Evergreen Review Presents: The Ferlinghetti Story" (Box 57)
    - "The Barry Farber Show," 1970 (Box 57)
  - 16MM (Box 58)
    - "Waiting for Godot, Dupe Negative, Parts 1 & 2" (Box 58)
    - "Waiting for Godot, Reel 3 of 3" (Box 58)
    - "Chant D'Amour," 2002 (Box 58)
    - "Grove Press "Personals" A & B Rolls" (Box 58)
  - Magnetic Tape
    - "Evergreen 7 ½ Master" (Box 58)
  - Digital Betacam
    - "Rosset Transfer: Reels 1-10 (Box 58)
    - "Rosset Transfer: Reels 11-13--"Film Outtakes" (Box 58)
    - "Strange Victory--Reels 1-7 (Box 58)
    - "Strange Victory--Reel 8" (Box 58)
  - Betacam SP
    - "Interview with Kenzaburo Oe," 1965 (2 tapes) (Box 58)
  - Magnetic Recording Tapes (Box 59)
    - "Barney Rosset Answering Questions by Professor E. R. Hutchison" (Box 59)
    - "The Barry Farber Show, Church League of America," 1970 (3 copies) (Box 59)
    - Unidentified (Box 59)
    - "Evergreen Review Presents: The Eye of Mexico," 1959 (Box 59)
    - "Not Part of Survey"
      - "S.F. Rejects--Evergreen Vol. 1, Vol. 2" (Box 59)
      - "Barney Reading to Peter" (Box 59)
      - "Gary Snyder Reading for Poetry" (Box 59)
      - "Not Without Words" (Box 59)
      - "Take One of 4 Track Tape at 7 ½ " p.s." (Box 59)
      - "Amos Tutola, The Palm Wine Drinkard" (Box 59)
  - VHS
    - "Rosset Reels 1-10" (Box 59)
  - Small 8mm Reels
    - "R1--Kentucky Derby," 1938 (empty box) (Box 59)
    - "R2--Auto Race" (Box 59)
    - "R3--Arlington Park" (ÀÀÀ) (Box 59)
  - Super 8
    - "Nicole on Swing," 1969 (Box 59)
  - Regular 8MM
    - "Fighting Words--Double O Films" (Box 59)
  - 2 Inch Tape Reels (Box 60)
    - "Waiting for Godot, Reel 1" (Box 60)
    - "Waiting for Godot, Reel 2" (Box 60)
  - DVDs
    - "Barney's Birthday--49 minutes" (Box 61, Folder A)
    - "Barney July 14th" (Box 61, Folder A)
    - "Barne's B-Day 2" (Box 61, Folder A)
    - "Red Bank"
      - "Barney Rosset, Jerry Tallmer," 2006 (Box 61, Folder A)
      - "Looper" (Box 61, Folder A)
      - "Not for Distribution--Some Flaws" (Box 61, Folder A)
      - "Old, Lower Quality but Complete" (Box 61, Folder A)
      - "Master DVD Red Bank," 2006 (Box 61, Folder A)
    - R to R--Double O
      - "Barney on E.R. Hutchinson, 1 of 4" (Box 61, Folder A)
      - "Very Good, 2 of 4" (Box 61, Folder A)
      - "3 of 4" (Box 61, Folder a)
      - "4 of 4" (Box 61, Folder A)
      - "Transcript of Barney Rosset respond to E.R. Hutchinson's Questions," (Floppy Disk) (Box 61, Folder a)
    - "Reel for Barney--Trailer for Obscene, Material Not in Film" (Box 61, Folder a)
    - "Barney & Archive" (Box 61, Folder a)
  - CDs
    - "Roger Tansey" (Box 61, Folder a)
    - "Barney's B-Day--East Hampton, 2006 (Box 61, Folder a)
    - "Barney Photos, 2008" (Box 61, Folder a)
    - "Wedding Photos, Regina & Charlie," 2007 (Box 61, Folder a)
    - "Photos--Memorial Day," 2004 (Box 61, Folder a)
    - "Astrid's Photos" (6 disks) (Box 61, Folder a)
  - 2 Inch Tape Reels
    - "Waiting for Godot, Reel 1--Edited" (Box 61, Folder B)
    - "Waiting for Godot, Reel 2--Edited" (Box 61, Folder C)
  - Film Reels (various formats) (Box 62)
    - Miscellaneous Strips of Film (Box 62)
    - "Chicago Race Track" (Box 62)
    - Unidentified ("R4 Heads") (Box 62)
    - "Coney Island" ("R6 Heads) (Box 62)
    - Unidentified ("R7 Heads") (Box 62)
    - "VJ Day" OR "Europe 1937 Barney and Parents" (R7) (Box 62)
    - "Luichow Air Base (R8 Heads) (Box 62)
    - "Peggy Coal Docks" (R9 Heads) (Box 62)
    - Barney Football (R10 Heads) (Box 62)
    - Unidentified ("R11 Heads") (Box 62)
    - "Gary Snyder Reads" OR EUROPE All the Nightmare" (Box 62)
  - DV-CAM
    - "Barney's 16MM Transfer"
      - "Reels 1-10" (Box 62)
      - "Reels 11-13" (Box 62)
    - "Barney Rosset Super 8 Transfer" (Box 62)
    - "Fighting Words--Double O Films," 2006 (Box 62)
  - MiniDV
    - "Rosset Interview on Robert Frank" (Box 62)
    - "Laos to Cambodia" (2 cassettes) (Box 62)
    - "Cambodia" (Box 62)
    - "Chiang Mai" (Box 62)
    - "Strange Victory--CUNY TV" (Box 62)
    - "Hampton Waters--Rosset, Potter, Stiles," 2006 (Box 62)
    - "Irish Arts Center--After at Home--Barney Reading" (Box 62)
    - "Christmas--New Year's," 2004 (Box 62)
    - "Immigrant Demonstration, May Day Union Square," 2006 (Box 62)
    - "Working Title--Shattered" (Box 62)
    - "Fighting Words--Double O Films" (Box 62)
    - "NY Independent Publishing Center" (Box 62)
    - "Genet" (Box 62)
    - "Michael McClure" (Box 62)
  - Super 8
    - "Fighting Words, CR #8" (Box 62)
    - "Fighting Words, CR #6-7" (Box 62)
    - "Peter's Grand Canyon River Trip, Summer 1969" (Box 62)
  - 16mm (Box 63)
    - Strange Victory--very good (Box 63)
    - Waiting for Godot (3 reels, in two plastic cases) (Box 63)
  - 8 35m Reels (Box 64)
    - Strange Victory--Composite Print (plus extra reel) (Box 64)
- Series VII: Files Used for Autobiography, 1936-2011
  This series was acquired shortly after Rosset's passing and contains his working files for his intended autobiography, The Subject is Left-Handed. Included here are background materials on Rosset, drafts of chapters, ephemera, photographs, audio-visual in various media formats, and correspondence. The folder titles have been retained but the files have been arranged in alphabetical order.
  - Audio-Visual Materials (Box 65)
    - CDs
      - Wedding Video, Undated (Box 65, Folder a)
      - Wedding Video--No Video Needs Fixing, 2007 (Box 65, Folder a)
    - MiniDV
      - "Rosset Transfer Reels 1-10," 2002 (Box 65, Folder a)
      - "Rosset Transfer CR# 11-13," 2002 (Box 65, Folder a)
      - "San Cristobal," February2008 (Box 65, Folder a)
      - "Genet," Undated (Box 65, Folder a)
      - "Oaxaca," January 2005 (3 Tapes) (Box 65, Folder a)
    - VHS Tapes
      - The Harder They Come (Box 65, Folder a)
      - Terry's Home Video, Roger Tansey Family, County Galway, Ireland (Box 65, Folder a)
      - Biography: The Gettys: A Tragedy of Riches (Box 65, Folder a)
      - Rampo (Box 65, Folder a)
      - Pool & Billiards (Box 65, Folder a)
      - L'Immortelle (Box 65, Folder a)
      - 60 Minutes: Sex (underage Girls) Thailand (Box 65, Folder a)
      - The Valley Obscured by Clouds (Box 65, Folder a)
      - Stirrings Still--Chris O'Neil (Box 65, Folder b)
      - The Sixth Sun (Box 65, Folder b)
      - Life Time Achievement Award, March2001 (Box 65, Folder b)
      - The Queen (Box 65, Folder b)
  - "AUTOBIO China Section," 2006-2011 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - "Autobio Correspondence," 2002-2009 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - "Autobio Materials Submitted to Algonquin," 2002-2004 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - "Auto-Bio Proposal," 2001-2006 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Autobiography Drafts
    - "Part One," 2006 Undated (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - "Part Two," 2008 Undated, (2 folders) (Box 66, Folder 6-7)
    - "Chapters 1 to 5," 2000s (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - "Chapters 6 to 13," 2000s (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - "Chapters 14 to 16," 2000s (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - "Chapters 17-24," 2000s, (2 folders) (Box 66, Folder 11-12)
  - "Beckett Chapter," 1990s-2007 Undated (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - "Beckett Working," 1990s-2000s (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - Blue Moon
    - "Sales Summary Blue Moon Books," 2002 Undated (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - "Blue Moon Catalogue Blue Notes," 1989-1996 (Box 66, Folder 16)
    - "Blue Moon Titles and Inventory and Production Schedule," 1990s (Box 66, Folder 17)
    - "Blue Moon Books Correspondence," 1996-1998 (Box 66, Folder 18)
    - "The Blue Moon Reader--Censorship," 1969-1992 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - "Blue Moon Sales," 1993-1997 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - "Blue Moon Sales 1999" 1999-2000 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - "Blue Moon Inventory," 1998-1999 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - "Blue Moon Covers (bound)," 1988 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - "Blue Moon Covers," Undated, (2 folders) (Box 67, Folder 6-7)
    - "Blue Moon," 1980s-1990s, (2 folders) (Box 67, Folder 8-9)
  - "Book II"
    - "Beats Chapter--Burroughs," 1962-2007 (Box 67, Folder 10)